youzee.com 2013-09-19

# Youzee

This Privacy Policy (together with the [Terms of Use](https://youzee.com/en/about/legal/terms-of-use) and other documents referred to therein) establishes the terms under which, in the event that we collect or you provide us with personal data during your experience on Youzee, whether through the URL address [http://www.youzee.com](http://www.youzee.com/) (hereinafter “the Website”) or via other digital media, formats or devices provided by Youzee (as a group, hereinafter “the Platform”), Youzee guarantees you its compliance with Organic Law 15/1999 of 13th December on the Protection of Personal Data (hereinafter the LOPD) and its implementing regulations. 

Whenever it is necessary for you to provide us with or for us to access your personal data, whether to supply you with all the facilities of our Platform when you register as a user or as a customer of our services, you must read this Privacy Policy and, if required, give us your consent so that we can process your data. 

##  Collection of data 

Through the Platform, Youzee can collect different types of personal data, that is, certain information that due to its characteristics will allow us to identify you and which is added to the file that we have duly registered before the General Data Protection Registry. 

We store the personal data that you supply us with when you register on our Platform, so that you can access the services provided by Youzee in any of their forms. 

We would ask that any personal data that you send us via the registration option are true, complete, and accurate and that they are always up-to-date. Youzee also hereby informs you that non-completion of the personal data requested in the Register section may prevent us from managing your Youzee service. 

Finally, we would like to remind you that in order to register at Youzee you must be at least 14 years of age and you may only contract our services if you are of legal age. That is why Youzee reserves the right to ask you for a photocopy of your National I.D. Card or any other document that accredits your age, in which case Youzee guarantees you that any personal data you supply us with in order to prove your age shall not be used for any other purpose than confirming your age. 

##  Purpose of the data processing 

Youzee processes your personal data in order to identify you as a user, give you access to Youzee and supply you with all the facilities for the provision of the services that we offer. To ensure the proper use of the Platform and our services, Youzee may keep certain minimum personal data of our users for a certain period of time after cancellation of the profile. 

Before using a new Youzee service, please remember to read the Terms of Use and the Contractual Conditions, and there you will be able to see if there is any specific term in the service where your personal data is processed in a special way. 

We may also use your data to keep you informed about new Youzee products and services through our Platform or the e-mail address that you have provided us with, to send you advertising or commercial information about our Platform, our services and/or products, as well as regarding special offers, promotions, activities etc. that we think may interest you. At Youzee we will be able to obtain profiles and segment our users based on the information that you have decided to supply us with, in order to personalise your relationship with Youzee and improve your experience. By accepting this Privacy Policy you give your consent and authorise us to carry out the processing of your personal data for the aforementioned purposes. 

You are entitled to object to Youzee using your data to send you commercial or promotional communications. If you do not wish to receive this type of information you can tell us at any time through the objection section that is provided in the Account section of your Preferences. 

##  Security measures 

In response to the concern of Youzee about guaranteeing the security and confidentiality of your personal data, we have adopted the security standards demanded by the personal data protection regulations and we have also installed all technical means within our power in order to avoid the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorised access or theft of the supplied personal data that is collected through the Platform. Nevertheless, you should bear in mind that security measures on the Internet are not impregnable. 

##  Configuration of your profile 

Youzee provides you with different privacy levels, so that you can determine the privacy of the information that you have decided to include in your profile. Therefore, you will be the person, under your sole responsibility, who decides who has access to your information. 

As a Youzee user you will be able to control the privacy of your profile and its various elements at all times, for example: your photo, titles that you recommend to your friends, reviews that you publish and/or the visibility of your favourite titles. In the configuration of your profile we give you instructions on how to control your privacy on different levels, depending on the type of content and your different categories. You are the sole party responsible for the privacy level that you choose. 

Please remember that, depending on the privacy level that you choose for your Youzee profile, only your friends on Youzee or on other social networks, or also other members of Youzee will be able to access your data and your profile information. 

If Youzee adds extra privacy levels, you will be duly notified of them in compliance with the contents herein. Youzee shall not be responsible under any circumstances for any claim related to the security levels chosen or related to access to your information by other users. 

Youzee does not control and therefore accepts no responsibility whatsoever for any possible collection and processing of users' information by other users or by third parties. 

##  Rights of users 

As a visitor, registered user or customer, you are entitled to access your personal data so that we can inform you how we process them and for what purposes, to notify us that we should rectify your personal data, object to us using your data for a specific activity or request that we cancel your data if you no longer wish Youzee to process them. 

To do this you can cancel you profile by using the Delete Account button in the Account section of your Preferences or send us a request indicating the right that you wish to exercise, a photocopy of your National I.D. Card or passport and including the reference “Data Protection” to Youzee at: Plaza Santa María Soledad Torres Acosta 2, 2ª planta, 28004, Madrid, or to the following e-mail address: [soporte@youzee.com](mailto:soporte@youzee.com). 

Last update: February 21th, 2012 

© 2010-2012 YOUZEE ENTERTAINMENT ESPAÑA, S.L. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
